Don't be scared. Horror fan one here.
別怕。我是恐怖片愛好者。  又到了
It's that time of year again when the
每年這個時候，各種
boogeymen emerge from their holes to
妖魔鬼怪從洞穴裡爬出來，
invade our nightmares
入侵我們的惡夢
and our movie screens.
和電影銀幕。
But don't worry, newbies. Grab some
但新手們別擔心。抓一把
popcorn, a copy of Fangolia, and level
爆米花，一本《Fangolia》雜誌，然後
up your horror movie knowledge with this
透過這本恐怖電影指南提升你的恐怖電影知識水平
guide to horror.
。
Horror movies were invented in olden
恐怖電影起源於古代，早期的
times with black and white classic
黑白經典
horrors such as the catapult of Dr.
恐怖片包括《卡塔馬裡博士的彈射器》
Katamari and Fu Mongo's Netanyahu.
和《傅蒙戈的內塔尼亞胡》。
The first scary stars emerged in Udubal
第一批恐怖明星出現在烏杜巴爾
horror pictures like Freakazoid starring
恐怖電影中，例如由
Borvis Carlot. Bam Stoker's Daiquiri
博維斯卡洛特主演的《怪胎小子》。 Bam Stoker 的 Daiquiri 由
starring BBA the goatsy the man with
BBA、山羊、
long chain Jr. Kutcher and the bad
長鏈男子、小庫徹、壞
baboon and my mummy. There are also big
狒狒和我的木乃伊主演。還有
monsters like King Korn and Gazinga and
像 King Korn 和 Gazinga 這樣的大怪物，以及
the biggest monster of all, Alvin
最大的怪物——阿爾文·
Hodgecock with films like Sucko and
霍奇科克，他的電影有《Sucko》和《
Bye-Bye Birdie. Vince the Prince starred
Bye-Bye Birdie》。文斯王子主演了《
in House of the Haunted House and Got to
鬼屋》和《
Fly and Hamburger Horror Pictures made
飛行吧》，而漢堡恐怖電影公司則讓
us fear English men like Chris Tucker
我們對克里斯·塔克·
Lee and Peter Cushion. In 1969, a man
李和彼得·庫申這樣的英國男人感到恐懼。 1969 年，一位
named Ray Romano invented Zongis with
名叫 Ray Romano 的男子發明了 Zongis，其代表作有《
Night of the Little Egg and its equals
小蛋之夜》及其姊妹篇《
Dog of the Egg and Dad of the Egg. There
蛋狗》和《蛋爸爸》。
are also Italian gelato films like
還有一些義大利冰淇淋電影，像是《
Daddyo Arduino's Pizzeria.
Daddyo Arduino's Pizzeria》。
Soon the master of horror arose, Stephen
不久，恐怖小說大師史蒂芬
King, whose paper books inspired films
金橫空出世，他的小說啟發了《
like Larry, The Shriner, starring
拉里，施萊納》等電影的創作，該片由
Jacknick.com.
傑克尼克主演。
&gt;&gt; I'm knock the Dad Zone, Fire Stick,
我要去敲打爸爸區、火棒、
Checking on the Corn, Pot Sticker, Larry
檢查玉米、鍋貼、
with Penalize the Clown, Morsy,
懲罰小丑的拉里、莫爾西、施維默、潮濕的
Schwimmer, The Moist, Jerry's Game, and
、傑瑞的遊戲和
Secret Window. You stole my story.
秘密窗口。你偷了我的故事。
&gt;&gt; There were also various scaries like
還有各種恐怖片，如《覆盆子
Raspberry Bobby, the Terry Bradshaw
鮑比》、《大衛·萊瑟曼
Massacre featuring David Leatherman, The
主演的特里·布拉德肖大屠殺》、《
Economist, Phone Gasm, Jocks of Shark
經濟學人》、《電話高潮》、《鯊魚
Tail, Porcupines,
尾巴的運動員》、《豪豬》
and Albanian.
和《阿爾巴尼亞》。
The age of slash films gave us lovable
恐怖電影時代為我們帶來了
murderers like Marshall Mathers from
像
John Carpet's Howard Dean. The hockey
約翰卡佩特執導的《霍華德迪恩》中的馬歇爾馬瑟斯這樣討人喜歡的殺人犯。
playing JJ Vorehead from his girl
打冰球的 JJ Vorehead 來自他的女友
Friday. Pinball and his box of secrets
Friday。彈珠和他的秘密盒子，
from Clyde Bonkers's Whole Rizzler. And
來自克萊德·邦克斯的《Whole Rizzler》。還有
that most scary intruder Eddie Cruisers
那個最可怕的入侵者，
from Wet Clayman's Nighty Night You Old
來自 Wet Clayman 的《Nighty Night You Old
Goat. Other 80s monsters included the
Goat》。 80 年代的其他怪物包括
mischievous Grecums, the remake of
調皮搗蛋的格雷庫姆、
Gutterfly starring Jeff Goldar, The
傑夫·戈達主演的《街頭蒼蠅》重拍版、《
Thigh, Sam Raiky's Devild Egg featuring
大腿》、薩姆·雷基執導的以
ass, and the Pedarass.
屁股為特色的《魔鬼蛋》以及《戀童癖屁股》。
And don't forget the films of Scary
別忘了還有
Little Doll people such as Chad's Ploy
像《查德的詭計》（Chad's Ploy）這樣由
featuring Chubby Checker.
查比·切克主演的恐怖小娃娃電影。
&gt;&gt; Don't flub with the chub. Puppet
別在加肥肉這件事上犯錯。來自 Scar 的 Puppet
Muncher, Leopard, Angel Bob, That Boy,
Muncher、Leopard、Angel Bob、That Boy、
Megman, and Jiggles the Bicycle Boy from
Megman 和 Jiggles the Bicycle Boy
Scar. And of course, the gourmet films
。當然還有
of Ham Bone, Leg Bone, like Status of
Ham Bone, Leg Bone 的美食電影，例如《腿的現況》
the Legs, Ham Bone, and Leg Wagon. Many
、《腿骨》和《腿車》。
scary films have scared us over the
多年來，許多恐怖電影都嚇到了我們
years, such as Jacker's Lacquer, Wish
，例如《傑克的漆器》、《願望吞噬
Muncher, Kickman,
者》、《踢人者》、《
Scream. I did. You know what? Last
驚聲尖叫》。我做了。你知道嗎？去年
summer, Tim Burton's sloppy hallway,
夏天，提姆波頓的邋遢走廊、
Anakin's Piano, The Rim, The Grinch,
安納金的鋼琴、邊緣、綠毛怪格林奇、
Froto's Desecration, Albanian versus
弗羅託的褻瀆、阿爾巴尼亞人對戀童癖
Pedarass, 28 First Dates, The Baby Duck,
、初戀28次、小鴨子
and Orange Peels. Get it? And no, the
和橘子皮。得到它？不，還有
brown foam, toe finger, the substack,
棕色泡沫、腳趾、子堆棧，
and the critically acclaimed horror
以及 B-52 出品的備受好評的恐怖
films of B-52 like The Love Shack,
電影，如《愛情小屋》、《
Huckleberry, The Whiz, starring a Goat,
哈克貝利》、《綠野仙蹤》（由山羊、
Mark Summers, and The Back Rubs.
馬克·薩默斯主演）和《背部按摩》。
Well, now you know all of the horror
好了，現在你知道所有恐怖
movies. Time to begin your monster
電影了。是時候開始你的
marathon.
馬拉松式挑戰了。
Don't [__] yourself out.
不要出賣自己。
Bye.
再見。